Zine Library PUNK011
People's Archive, MLK Library
Zine Library Collection
1974-2011
People's Archive, MLK Library
PUNK011
3 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1
  - Another state of mind, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Binary load lifter, Number 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Special European Vacation Issue; May only be the front page and back page of the zine
  - Boogins, The, Volume 1, Number 1, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Fall Issue
  - Boogins, The, Volume 1, Number 2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Boogins, The, Volume 1, Number 3, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Boogins, The, Volume 1, Number 7, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Autumn Issue
  - Brand new age, Number 2, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bright-eyed crowd, Number 1, 2012-07 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bright-eyed crowd, Number 2, 2012-08 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brimming rag, Number 1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Capitol crisis, Number 1, 1980-11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Capitol crisis, Number 3, 1981-02 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Capitol crisis, Number 4, 1981-03 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Capitol crisis, Number 5, 1981-05 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cramhole, Number 1, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cramhole, Number 2, 2008-02 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cramhole, Number 3, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Crawl or die!, Number 1, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - DC Punk Presents Nation of Ulysses, Part 1: '88-'90, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - DC Punk Presents The Warmers, Part 1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - DC Punk Presents The Warmers, Part 1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Unfinished Rough
  - For those concerned, Number 1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Girls Rock! DC showcase, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Girls Rock! DC showcase, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Girls Rock! DC showcase, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Girls Rock! Official guide to rock, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Give me back, Number 1, 2007-02 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Give me back, Number 4, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Give me back, Number 5, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Late winter issue
  - Give me back, Number 5, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Greed, Volume 1, Number 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Greed, Volume 1, Number 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Greed magazine, Number 5, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Greed magazine, Number 6, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - groffiti, Number 6, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - groffiti, Number 8, 1974-02-04 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - groffiti, Number 9, 1974-02-18 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - groffiti, Number 10, 1974-03-03 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Grown ups are obsolete, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hands up!, Number 2, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hands up!, Number 3, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Winter issue
  - Held like sound, Number 6, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Spring issue
  - Held like sound, Number 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Highway, Number 2, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Summer/Fall
  - Hit and run, Number 1, 1977-07 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - I am eye, Number 1, 1983-12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - If this goes on, Number 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - If this goes on, Number 3, 1983-06 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Innervoid, Number 6, 1984-12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Insurrection, Number 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interrobang, Number 6, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Maximum rocknroll, 1988-11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mole, Number 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    winter
  - Mole, Number 4, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mole, Number 5, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mole, Number 6, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    2 copies
  - Mole, Number 7, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mole, Number 12, 1999-05 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mole, Number 13, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Most things suck, Volume 4, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - My rules photozine, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Noise works magazine, Volume 1, Number 4, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Off center, Number 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Off center, Number 3, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Off center, Number 4, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Papas, The, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Positive Youth Fest 5, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Positive Youth Fest 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Shotgun seamstress zine collection, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Slanted, Number 2, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Slickzine, Volume 2, Number 6, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Slickzine, Volume 2, Number 7, 1984-02 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Slickzine, Volume 2, Number 8, 1984-12 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Slickzine, Volume 3, Number 1, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Slickzine, Volume 3, Number 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Slickzine, Volume 4, Number 1, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Slickzine, Volume 4, Number 2, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Spectrum, Number 1, 2008-04 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State of the union, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Suburban Outcast, Number 2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Suspect Device, Number 1, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - To hell with good intentions fanzine, Number 15, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - To hell with good intentions fanzine, Number 16, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - To hell with good intentions fanzine, Number 17, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - To hell with good intentions fanzine, Number 18, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Thrillseeker, Number 2, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Thrillseeker, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Truly needy, Volume 2, Number 4, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Truly needy, Volume 2, Number 5, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Truly Needy, Number 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Turn around, Number 2, 1986-12 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Uno mas, Volume 1, Number 1, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Uno mas, Number 3, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 6, 1984-12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 7, 1985-01 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 8, 1985-04 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 9, 1985-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Volume number does not appear on the zine but is based on other issues in sequence
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 11, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 12, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - WDC period, Volume 1, Number 13, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Who cares?, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Word on the Street, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Yet another unslanted opinion, Number 1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Yet another unslanted opinion, Number 2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Yet another unslanted opinion, Number 5, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Zone V, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)